

LENSON KIARIE KARURU

Phone NO: +97466709571 972, Matarqadeem, Doha Lensonkiarie@gmail.com

# Objective

overall work experience has given me an opportunity to gather a broad range of skills and expertise that are highly valued in many industries ability to coordinate complex tasks, communicate effectively with various stakeholders, solve problems quickly and efficiently make up a valuable asset to any organization.

## **Skills & Abilities**

Problem solving skills, Data analysis and Visualization, Troubleshooting, maintenance skills, Excellent communication skills

# Experience

# **Lodige Systems Middle East 2018 – 2023**

Maintenance coordinator, Maintenance Technician

- Preparing daily reports and implement policies to maximize performance
- Ensuring all administrative records are completed accurately
- Procurement, storage handling and material review for relevant requirements and standards
- Data analysis for KPIs, equipment SLAs and audits from external and internal facility managements
- Performing maintenance, modification, and repair of cargo handling, conveyor, elevator, and lifting systems at HIA complexes DFWH, AMH, CARGO
- Fault diagnosis

# Kenya power and lightning Company 2017 – 2018

Installer

- Assembly, disassembly and testing of inhemeters.
- Wiring and termination of electrical components
- Installation of inhemeters, testing, adjustment and commissioning

## Education

## **Technical university of Kenya-High diploma**

Electrical Engineering –2016-2017

JKUAT - Nairobi-Degree

Bachelors in information technology-In progress

	Cisco Academy- Security Network-2021-2023 Data science- 2023
COMMUNITY INVOLVMENT	FIFA WORLD CUP 2022- assistant manager HOC Operations AMIRCUP2022-Marshall FIFA ARAB CUP2021-Team leader Spectator services
Personal data	Gender-Male Birth Date-08/07/1997 Marital status-Engaged Languages-English, Kiswahili
ADDITIONAL SKILLS	MS suite, SQL, ERP, EAM Software, packet tracer, Python